LAWRENCE DASS

CONTACT

987 351 2848
Github - Lawrence4code
LawrencePro.dev@gmail.com
www.LawrencePro.dev

NA-301, Shriram Smrithi, Sarjapura-Attibele Road, Bidaraguppe, Bengaluru, Karnataka - 562107

ABOUT ME

MERN Stack Developer with experience in developing interfaces, interactions, and applications from scratch across the web with expertise in JavaScript, React, and NodeJS for the backend scripting.

Ever-Curious, tech-malleable, and driven with a passion for creating engaging immersive interactions.

Certified Full Stack Developer from Coding Elements and Frontend Nano Degree from Udacity.

EDUCATION

CBSE SENIOR SECONDARY EDUCATION

2004 - 2006 | D.T.E.A Senior Secondary School, New Delhi

BACHELOR OF COMMERCE

2009-2012 | Jagruti Degree & P.G collage, Hydrabad

POST GRADUATE DIPLOMA IN INFORMATION SECURITY

2019-Persuing | Indira Gandhi National Open University, New Delhi

EXPERIENCE

2014 CVENT INDIA, GURGAON (2013 — 2014)

PRODUCT CONSULTANT

Support for event management application.
Assistance with event management, email support, and event websites.

2018 AMERICAN EXPRESS, GURGAON (2014 — 2018) SENIOR CREDIT SPECIALIST/ACCOUNT ANALYST

Account analysis for customer spending behavior and location & regional data analysis (Reporting with SQL database) for open market opportunity, product design, and consultation.

2020 EDFORA - myPat.in (2019 — 2020)

SOFTWARE ENGINEER

I worked on the flagship product of Edfora i.e. myPat.in which is build with MEAN Stack. myPat.in is web app where student can take test and get in-depth analysis and performance tracking. My core responsibility was Frontend part of the application with Angular and backend with ExpressJS (Node) and MongoDB.

SKILLS

HTML5 ReactJS CSS3/SASS MongoDB

JavaScript Webpack/ParcelJS

Angular CSS framworks (Bootstrap & NodeJS Meterial CSS, tailwindCSS)

Git

Please visit LawrencePro.dev for projects and Git repositories.